[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120821pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 46, "question": "When you heard Todd Akin's comments, what was your reaction?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NNS", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 47, "answer": "Well, both that what he said was actually inaccurate and also very dangerous.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Todd Akin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120821pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 60, "question": "ORGAN: How would you have felt if you had been compelled to have that baby by the rapist who raped you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 61, "answer": "Well, that is the key point.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Supreme Court"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "120821pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBD", ",", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 114, "question": "Isn't that what a modern America should stand for?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "WP", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 115, "answer": "You know, modern America has said, according to the Supreme Court, that it is cruel and unusual punishment to give the death penalty for rapists.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120821pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 144, "question": "Why should that woman who feels that strongly the other way to you not have the same right that you did?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 145, "answer": "You know, I may not look the same as I did when I was 4 years old or 4 weeks old unborn in my mother's womb.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120821pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "EX", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 181, "question": "Well, what good is my right to anything as a woman if I don't have my right to life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 182, "answer": "Well, let me just tell you, there -- you brought up people in a coma.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120821pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "VBZ", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "JJS", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 315, "question": "And what does it mean for the presidential battle?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 316, "answer": "Well, obviously, what he said is despicable and outrageous, and it's good at least to see his own party trying to banish him from the race.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120821pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 334, "question": "What is the core of the problem for America incorporated, when you look at it, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 335, "answer": "You know, Piers, what we've really argued in this book is we didn't get here by accident.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120821pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "CD", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "JJ", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 355, "question": "I mean, what -- when you look at the Ryan Budget Plan, Romney's amendment of that, you look at what President Obama is saying, what do you think is the most sensible way forward for America to finance all this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "WP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 356, "answer": "You know, there's no question to me that we have to agree on one thing, that the only way to deal with the budget deficit that big is with both tax revenue and spending cuts.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Romney", "Obama"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120821pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 379, "question": "Tom, when you hear Romney talking tough on Iran, and we've also got the Syria situation bubbling away as well, do you think that the Romney/Ryan ticket has enough foreign policy experience to know what to do about these two crises?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "WP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 380, "answer": "I think they have an incredibly weak foreign policy biography between the two of them and a rather weak team, frankly.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Iran", "Syria"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120821pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 389, "question": "And why shouldn't they assume it will be coming their way?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 390, "answer": "Well, you know, it's a very legitimate question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Syria", "Libya"]}, "docId": "120821pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", "NNS", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 413, "question": "Isn't it time that somebody did something?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 414, "answer": "The problem with Syria is that unlike other Arab awakening revolutions -- you know, Libya imploded.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120821pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 459, "question": "How are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 460, "answer": "I'm well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120821pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 461, "question": "Yourself?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "."], "aSentId": 462, "answer": "Here's the thing, I'm a Christian, you're a Christian.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120821pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 465, "question": "Do you feel that being Christian has become almost a bad word in a country that's still predominantly Christian?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "JJ", "NNS", "VBN", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 466, "answer": "We have a branding problem probably.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120821pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "NNS", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 507, "question": "Has he lived up to the expectation, hopes that you had?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 508, "answer": "Well, here's the -- I mean, I always avoided politics, especially as a comedian because you're alienating half the thing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120821pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 524, "question": "For you, Romney is the more likely of the candidates?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "RBR", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 525, "answer": "He's a successful businessman.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Romney"]}}]